name: 'Jobs (Word - Translation)'
questions:
  -
    question: 'a student'
    answers:
      - учитель
      - студент
      - учиться
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'an assistant'
    answers:
      - продавец
      - менеджер
      - 'ассистент / помощник'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'a doctor'
    answers:
      - медсестра
      - медврач
      - врач
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'a factory worker'
    answers:
      - 'фабричный рабочий'
      - грузчик
      - 'офисный работник'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'a waiter'
    answers:
      - секретарь
      - продавец
      - официант
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'a policewoman'
    answers:
      - полицейский
      - политик
      - женщина-полицейский
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'a teacher'
    answers:
      - ученик
      - учитель
      - профессор
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'a nurse'
    answers:
      - медсестра
      - врач
      - секретарь
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'a salesperson'
    answers:
      - ассистент
      - 'заводской рабочий'
      - продавец
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'a lawyer'
    answers:
      - юрист
      - администратор
      - официант
    correct: 1
  -
    question: waitress
    answers:
      - юрист
      - официантка
      - официант
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'a policeman'
    answers:
      - женщина-полицейский
      - полицейский
      - политик
    correct: 2
